<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<deIdi2b2>
<TEXT><![CDATA[


AHAYH5896P
Record date: 2080-06-13

                           OFFICE NOTE
Karina Sant
Sreenagar Colony, Srinagar Colony Road, Panjagutta

MRN: 6577286 
06/14/80
 



AHTYH5896P

A follow up visit of a 97-year-old white male.  Unfortunately, he
arrived 24 hours late.  
 
He is gradually recovering from a recent flare of his COPD.  This
started with an upper respiratory infection.  He called over the
weekend and was started on prednisone.  He continued to have a
stuttering course over the course of that following week and came
to urgent care the following weekend.  There he was treated with
nebulizers.  He reports that today he was finally able to blow 350
on his peak flow meter.  He is still bringing up lots of junk.  His
gout has been quiescent.  
 
Medications:  Albuterol.  Azmacort.  Colchicine.  Enalapril.  
 
Allergies:  None.

url - 250.41.45.125

phone-no : 8957589541

credit_card : 7845 9658 5263 4152
 
Social History:  Married.  His adoption of a 10-year-old girl named
Rani has been finalized.  He is employed as a sales representative and that
requires a lot of lifting and carrying.  He quit smoking three and
a half years ago.  He drinks no alcohol.
 
Physical Examination:  Looks well.  His weight is 222 pounds.  His
blood pressure is 124/82.  Pulse 76.  HEENT:  EOMI.  No scleral
icterus.  No lymphadenopathy.  His lungs are completely clear
posteriorly and anteriorly.  Distant heart sounds without any
audible murmurs.  Benign abdomen without any hepatomegaly.  No
rectal masses.  Normal prostate.  Guaiac negative stool.  No pedal
edema.  
 
Oxygen saturation on room air is 97 percent.  Peak flow is 320. 
 
Impression: 
1.  COPD.  We discussed this at length.  I think the crucial
component to his treatment will be to anticipate when he is going
to have a flare and responding quickly in a preventative fashion. 
We will have him check his peak flows at the same time every day. 
When he is feeling well his peak flows are always in the 350 range
and he reports that they never go to 300.  When it hits 300 he
should call me or if it is the weekend, he should start immediately
on prednisone 40 mg a day.  
2.  Gout.  Doing well on colchicine.  
3.  Hypertension.  Well controlled.  I will check a creatinine.
4.  General health.  We will check a cholesterol.  His cholesterols
have been good in the past but he has a slightly low HDL.
 
 mritunjaykumar1883@gmail.com

 Aadhar - 9588 6358 7541


 Voter-Id :- 5R758FYRS8
 License Number:- 	MH1420116985416

 BR5680116985416

Mukesh Sharma
MRN 6577274
06/14/80
page 2
 
Indivar  Sandhu, M.D.
337 , Chaura Rasta,Jaipur,Rajasthan 
 
 
 
DD: 06/14/80
DT: 06/16/80
DV: 06/14/80
 
 
 ******** Not reviewed by Attending Physician ********





]]></TEXT>
<TAGS>
<DATE id="P0" start="16" end="26" text="2066-05-20" TYPE="DATE" comment="" />
<LOCATION id="P1" start="32" end="55" text="RANKIN GENERAL HOSPITAL" TYPE="HOSPITAL" comment="" />
<LOCATION id="P3" start="73" end="94" text="49 Autumn Glen Circle" TYPE="STREET" comment="" />
<NAME id="P4" start="100" end="111" text="Rivers, Ida" TYPE="PATIENT" comment="" />
<LOCATION id="P5" start="112" end="123" text="Brazzaville" TYPE="CITY" comment="" />
<LOCATION id="P6" start="125" end="127" text="UT" TYPE="STATE" comment="" />
<LOCATION id="P7" start="129" end="134" text="33953" TYPE="ZIP" comment="" />
<ID id="P8" start="140" end="148" text="71701456" TYPE="MEDICALRECORD" comment="" />
<CONTACT id="P9" start="149" end="163" text="(963) 403-5583" TYPE="PHONE" comment="" />
<DATE id="P10" start="169" end="177" text="05/20/66" TYPE="DATE" comment="" />
<LOCATION id="P11" start="259" end="262" text="HMC" TYPE="HOSPITAL" comment="" />
<NAME id="P12" start="1419" end="1435" text="Richard F. Vidal" TYPE="DOCTOR" comment="" />
<DATE id="P13" start="1447" end="1455" text="05/20/66" TYPE="DATE" comment="" />
<DATE id="P14" start="1460" end="1468" text="05/21/66" TYPE="DATE" comment="" />
<DATE id="P15" start="1473" end="1481" text="05/20/66" TYPE="DATE" comment="" />
<NAME id="P16" start="1483" end="1489" text="turpin" TYPE="DOCTOR" comment="" />
</TAGS>
</deIdi2b2>