{"content": "Mrs. Shalini visited Dinanath Mangeshkar Hospital, Pune.,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":51,"end":54,"text":"Pune"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":21,"end":48,"text":"Dinanath Mangeshkar Hospital"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":5,"end":11,"text":"Shalini"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482729000,"last_updated_at":1576482729000,"sec_taken":14,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Her physician was Dr Arun Wardhan and she was happy with results of ETT. ,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":21,"end":32,"text":"Arun Wardhan"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482415000,"last_updated_at":1576482415000,"sec_taken":7,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Manisha was in Cardiac rehab locally at Indore last week and BP 170/80.  They called us and we increased her HCTZ to 25 mg from 12.5 mg.  States her BP's were fine there since - 130-140/70-80.,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":40,"end":45,"text":"Indore"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":0,"end":6,"text":"Manisha"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481604000,"last_updated_at":1576481604000,"sec_taken":23,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Patient Mrs. Harshita presents for uri. Walks in Mumbai branch of Sassoon Hopital.  Overdue for follow-up by 3 months.Started last week.   Sinus pressure, post nasal drip , headache , ears blocked.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":13,"end":20,"text":"Harshita"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482877000,"last_updated_at":1576482877000,"sec_taken":11,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Thyroid nodule : 2065, thyroid scan 2066 consistent with hot nodule and toxic multinodular goiter, saw Dr Rakesh Yadav, follow TSH.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":106,"end":117,"text":"Rakesh Yadav"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481938000,"last_updated_at":1576481938000,"sec_taken":8,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Patient Mrs. Sharddha Kapoor has appointment with Dr Dinesh More in Delhi","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":53,"end":63,"text":"Dinesh More"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":13,"end":27,"text":"Sharddha Kapoor"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482178000,"last_updated_at":1576482178000,"sec_taken":12,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "It was in April at AIIMS, Delhi and she went to discuss treatment of the subclinical hyperthyroidism,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":19,"end":23,"text":"AIIMS"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482471000,"last_updated_at":1576482471000,"sec_taken":10,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Patient Mr. Anil Tawde is instructed to make follow-up appointments with his cardiac surgeon.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":12,"end":15,"text":"Anil"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482685000,"last_updated_at":1576482685000,"sec_taken":8,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "His surgeon was Dr. Ritesh Prasad for two weeks. Following his discharge from the Sahyadri Hospital in Bengaluru,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":103,"end":111,"text":"Bengaluru"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":82,"end":98,"text":"Sahyadri Hospital"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":20,"end":32,"text":"Ritesh Prasad"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482832000,"last_updated_at":1576482832000,"sec_taken":15,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "He returned to see his primary care physician , Dr. Anurag Sethi one to two weeks following discharge from the Kokilaben Dhirubhai Ambani Hospital, Lucknow,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":148,"end":154,"text":"Lucknow"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":111,"end":145,"text":"Kokilaben Dhirubhai Ambani Hospital"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":52,"end":63,"text":"Anurag Sethi"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576483097000,"last_updated_at":1576483097000,"sec_taken":17,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Ms. Seema Bhatia was detected with breast cancer when CT Scan was done by Dr. Aman Siddhartha at Nehru Hospital, Dehradun.,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":113,"end":120,"text":"Dehradun"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":97,"end":110,"text":"Nehru Hospital"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":78,"end":92,"text":"Aman Siddhartha"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":15,"text":"Seema Bhatia"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482801000,"last_updated_at":1576482801000,"sec_taken":18,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient underwent a colonoscopy at Tata Main Hospital, Tatanagar and a mass was noted in the transverse colon. A biopsy was taken and the results are not known but were reported to Dr. Ramesh Joshi as colon cancer.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":189,"end":200,"text":"Ramesh Joshi"}]},{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":59,"end":67,"text":"Tatanagar"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":39,"end":56,"text":"Tata Main Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482906000,"last_updated_at":1576482906000,"sec_taken":22,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Patient is a 73 year old male named Atik Qureshi who immigrated from Bangladesh approximately fifteen years ago.,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":69,"end":78,"text":"Bangladesh"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":36,"end":47,"text":"Atik Qureshi"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482164000,"last_updated_at":1576482164000,"sec_taken":13,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mrs. Preeti Wakharia is a 63-year-old , insulin-dependent diabetic with a long history of peripheral vascular disease as well as multiple surgical procedures.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":5,"end":19,"text":"Preeti Wakharia"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576483063000,"last_updated_at":1576483063000,"sec_taken":11,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "she was discharged to the K.E.M Hospital in Amritsar , where she was making progress in physical therapy and rehabilitation.,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":44,"end":51,"text":"Amritsar"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":26,"end":39,"text":"K.E.M Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481869000,"last_updated_at":1576481869000,"sec_taken":15,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The absence of pulses persisted over the course of the night , after which point she was referred back to Sanjeevani Hospital for evaluation. She denies any significant pain or any other complications.,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":106,"end":124,"text":"Sanjeevani Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482562000,"last_updated_at":1576482562000,"sec_taken":18,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "She will follow with Dr. Neeta Rane at Aurangabad in one to two weeks.,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":39,"end":48,"text":"Aurangabad"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":25,"end":34,"text":"Neeta Rane"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482243000,"last_updated_at":1576482243000,"sec_taken":16,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Specific care should be given to his insulin regimen as well as his behavior control and nutrition as noted in the discharge instructions. Again please c.c. Dr. Vivek Alatkar on this discharge summary,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":161,"end":173,"text":"Vivek Alatkar"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482770000,"last_updated_at":1576482770000,"sec_taken":16,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mr. Mahesh Mahajan is a 74-year-old man with severe venous stasis , CHF with an EF of 60% , atrial fibrillation on Coumadin , COPD , history post surgical debridement , who presents with shortness of breath and left lower extremity cellulitis of severe left lower extremity cellulitis in March 2006 status,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":17,"text":"Mahesh Mahajan"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482930000,"last_updated_at":1576482930000,"sec_taken":22,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient has a living sister , Dina Jambhekar who has cancer. She is his healthcare proxy. Her phone number is 199-347-1999.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":34,"end":47,"text":"Dina Jambhekar"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481711000,"last_updated_at":1576481711000,"sec_taken":13,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mr. Ibrahim Sheikh is a 74-year-old man living in Punjab has severe venous stasis , CHF ,atrial fibrillation requiring Coumadin , COPD , severe left lower extremity cellulitis status post surgical debridement who presents with shortness of breath and recurrent left lower extremity cellulitis.,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":50,"end":55,"text":"Punjab"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":17,"text":"Ibrahim Sheikh"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576483136000,"last_updated_at":1576483136000,"sec_taken":16,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient is DNR/DNI. Pressors are okay. Healthcare proxy is Reema Raj who is his sister 199-347-1999.Consults Dr. Akash Khanna,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":117,"end":128,"text":"Akash Khanna"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":63,"end":71,"text":"Reema Raj"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482753000,"last_updated_at":1576482753000,"sec_taken":11,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Dr. Faheem Ansari diagnosed patient with vericose veins at Sahara Hospital in Kashmir,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":78,"end":84,"text":"Kashmir"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":59,"end":73,"text":"Sahara Hospital"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":16,"text":"Faheem Ansari"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482963000,"last_updated_at":1576482963000,"sec_taken":23,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Dr. Mihir Koushal of the Hiranandani Hospital in Chennai is the physician of the current patient ,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":49,"end":55,"text":"Chennai"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":25,"end":44,"text":"Hiranandani Hospital"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":16,"text":"Mihir Koushal"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481929000,"last_updated_at":1576481929000,"sec_taken":24,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Dr.Nitesh Rajput working at the Medanta Hsopital, Kerala said by the morning of November , 2003 , the patient had received a total of five units of packed red blood cells due to blood loss secondary to this hematoma,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":50,"end":55,"text":"Kerala"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":32,"end":47,"text":"Medanta Hsopital"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":3,"end":15,"text":"Nitesh Rajput"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482119000,"last_updated_at":1576482119000,"sec_taken":49,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Dr. Sunil Batra was the radiologist for patient in Lilavati Hospital, Palampur,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":70,"end":77,"text":"Palampur"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":51,"end":67,"text":"Lilavati Hospital"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":14,"text":"Sunil Batra"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482857000,"last_updated_at":1576482857000,"sec_taken":24,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mr. Girdhar Naik has post 2-vessel coronary artery bypass grafting in 6/13 , hypertension , atrial fibrillation status post cardioversion on Coumadin , hypercholesterolemia , aortic stenosis , status post aortic valve replacement with bioprosthetic valve at the","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":10,"text":"Girdhar"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481671000,"last_updated_at":1576481671000,"sec_taken":8,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Admission laboratory values included a Chem-7 within normal limits with a creatinine of 0.8 and glucose of 181. White blood cell count of 9.8 , hematocrit of 33.6 , and platelets of 222 with a differential of 88% neutrophils.,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":0,"end":19,"text":"Admission laboratory"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481997000,"last_updated_at":1576481997000,"sec_taken":24,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Ms. Dube is a 58-year-old female status post stent to her left circumflex coronary artery three months prior to admission , with a history of non-insulin dependent diabetes mellitus , hyperlipidemia , hypertension , who presents with left jaw pain for the last several days.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":7,"text":"Dube"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482385000,"last_updated_at":1576482385000,"sec_taken":10,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient was thought by hematology to have these hematomas secondary to over anticoagulation with Lovenox , Plavix , aspirin and possible SANE MEDICAL CENTER trial drug with a Karim Medical Center,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":179,"end":198,"text":"Karim Medical Center"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":141,"end":159,"text":"SANE MEDICAL CENTER"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481821000,"last_updated_at":1576481821000,"sec_taken":16,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Prior to her catheterization she was enrolled in the Krishna General Hospital,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":53,"end":76,"text":"Krishna General Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482150000,"last_updated_at":1576482150000,"sec_taken":29,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "This was a blinded trial with Mother Teresa Hospital, Kolkata's inhibitor. In accordance with the trial , the patient was started on Lovenox 1 mg per kg subcutaneously b.i.d.,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":54,"end":60,"text":"Kolkata"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":30,"end":51,"text":"Mother Teresa Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576483051000,"last_updated_at":1576483051000,"sec_taken":48,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Please call Dr. Narendra Deshmukh immediately to schedule follow-up appointment ,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":16,"end":32,"text":"Narendra Deshmukh"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481785000,"last_updated_at":1576481785000,"sec_taken":21,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Please see primary care doctor Dr. Amit Nanda in 2-3 weeks for medication management ,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":35,"end":44,"text":"Amit Nanda"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482374000,"last_updated_at":1576482374000,"sec_taken":7,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Patient was admitted to the Shri Ganga Ram Medical Center's surgery service after undergoing LRYGB.,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":33,"end":56,"text":"Ganga Ram Medical Center"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482039000,"last_updated_at":1576482039000,"sec_taken":19,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient was given explicit instructions to follow-up in clinic with Dr. Dilip Doshi at Banaras in 1-2 weeks,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":91,"end":97,"text":"Banaras"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":76,"end":86,"text":"Dilip Doshi"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481697000,"last_updated_at":1576481697000,"sec_taken":16,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "He presented to Dr. Adityanath Mani's office today with complaints of nausea and vomiting for 24-48 hours and mild abdominal pain , mid epigastric.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":20,"end":36,"text":"Adityanath Mani's"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482782000,"last_updated_at":1576482782000,"sec_taken":10,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Kritika Nair,the patient is a 74-year-old woman with a past medical history significant for rectosigmoid cancer complicated with vesicular vaginal fistula status post total pelvic exenteration , cystectomy with ileal loop diversion on February 2004 , obesity , hypoventilation syndrome with chronic respiratory acidosis status post gluteal sacral abscess who was brought to the Emergency Department from a skilled nursing facility with change in mental status and sacral wound infection.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":0,"end":11,"text":"Kritika Nair"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481763000,"last_updated_at":1576481763000,"sec_taken":29,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient Disha Nayak is a 54-year-old woman with history of asthma/COPD , morbid obesity , obstructive sleep apnea , but does not tolerate BiPAP who presented to the emergency room with worsening somnolence.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":11,"end":22,"text":" Disha Nayak"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482093000,"last_updated_at":1576482093000,"sec_taken":23,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Dhanashree Dixit, 55 y/o female with h/o obesity , OSA , asthma , CVA w/ LLE weakness , DM2 ( periph neuropathy and charcot foot ) , MI in 1987 but no CAD by cath , normal MIBI in 3/6 , EF55% , smoking and anemia of unknown etiology , presents with 2 weeks of progressive SOB.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":0,"end":15,"text":"Dhanashree Dixit"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482197000,"last_updated_at":1576482197000,"sec_taken":9,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Tanmay Garg is a 38 year old man with congestive heart failure and abdominal pain for 48 hours.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":0,"end":10,"text":"Tanmay Garg"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482257000,"last_updated_at":1576482257000,"sec_taken":30,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "He presented to Dr. Arvind Kumar at his Hyderbad office in PGIMER Hospital today with complaints of nausea and vomiting for 24-48 hours and mild abdominal pain , mid epigastric. About two weeks ago , the patient developed upper respiratory symptoms , cough , low grade temperature , malaise.,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":59,"end":73,"text":"PGIMER Hospital"}]},{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":40,"end":47,"text":"Hyderbad"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":20,"end":31,"text":"Arvind Kumar"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482585000,"last_updated_at":1576482585000,"sec_taken":21,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Via Dr. Gurpreet Chaddha , abdominal pain is a sign of the patient's congestive heart failure.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":8,"end":23,"text":"Gurpreet Chaddha"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481842000,"last_updated_at":1576481842000,"sec_taken":11,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Left ventriculogram showed 35% with 3+ mitral regurgitation thought secondary to idiopathic familial and ETOH , followed by Dr. Rajesh Menon .,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":128,"end":139,"text":"Rajesh Menon"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481679000,"last_updated_at":1576481679000,"sec_taken":7,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Cardiomyopathy service , Dr. Jagdish Shergil , attending , began following patient on the first hospital day at Tanveer Hospital, Bhilai.,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":130,"end":135,"text":"Bhilai"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":112,"end":127,"text":"Tanveer Hospital"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":29,"end":43,"text":"Jagdish Shergil"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482069000,"last_updated_at":1576482069000,"sec_taken":28,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Patient Rana Mahaveer is being discharged home with VNA services. He will follow up with Dr. Shamali Singh on 11 of August at 9:20 A.M.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":93,"end":105,"text":"Shamali Singh"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":8,"end":20,"text":"Rana Mahaveer"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482366000,"last_updated_at":1576482366000,"sec_taken":10,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "She has followup appointments with her primary care provider , Dr. Garima Sharma , and also with the Govind General Surgery Clinic regarding possible cholecystectomy.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":67,"end":79,"text":"Garima Sharma"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482938000,"last_updated_at":1576482938000,"sec_taken":7,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mr. Sachin Negi is a 60-year-old man with a known history of ischemic cardiomyopathy and CHF , EF of 35% , status post CABG in 1990 with redo in July 2005 , as well as mitral and tricuspid valve repair and left atrial reconstruction in July 2005.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":14,"text":"Sachin Negi"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482529000,"last_updated_at":1576482529000,"sec_taken":18,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "On further questioning , Mr. Sameer Rai reported symptoms of increasing dyspnea on exertion with decreased exercise tolerance as well as chronic loose stools with a history of C-diff positivity but negative on last testing.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":29,"end":38,"text":"Sameer Rai"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481643000,"last_updated_at":1576481643000,"sec_taken":8,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mr. Chirag Hasan's covering PCP was spoken to by Dr. Dinesh Verma and recomended that he see his PCP next week for video swallow and EDG referal.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":53,"end":64,"text":"Dinesh Verma"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":17,"text":"Chirag Hasan's"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482815000,"last_updated_at":1576482815000,"sec_taken":13,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient was discharged home on November with followup with Dr. Mathur and Dr. Singhania at the For Nali Hospital, Trivendram.,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":118,"end":127,"text":"Trivendram"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":103,"end":115,"text":"Nali Hospital"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":82,"end":90,"text":"Singhania"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":67,"end":72,"text":"Mathur"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482407000,"last_updated_at":1576482407000,"sec_taken":21,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mr. Ajinkya Giridhar  is a 59-year-old gentleman with no known history of cardiac disease who presented with substernal chest pain.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":19,"text":"Ajinkya Giridhar"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482594000,"last_updated_at":1576482594000,"sec_taken":9,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mr. Pratik Dhillon was in his usual state of health with known cardiac risk factors of hypertension , peripheral vascular disease family history , and history of smoking cigarettes who presented with steady course of substernal chest pain beginning the day of admission.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":17,"text":"Pratik Dhillon"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481852000,"last_updated_at":1576481852000,"sec_taken":9,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Upon arrival in the Emergency Department of PGIMER Hospital at Haridwar, the patient received sublingual Nitroglycerin as well as Lopressor , Nitropaste , and Aspirin with resolution of symptoms.,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":63,"end":70,"text":"Haridwar"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":44,"end":58,"text":"PGIMER Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481803000,"last_updated_at":1576481803000,"sec_taken":16,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Madhuri is a 65-year-old woman with coronary risk factors of diabetes mellitus , insulin dependent diabetes , hypertension , age , and elevated cholesterol , who was admitted to the Cardiology Service at Birla Hospital in Noida after a syncope in vascular clinic.,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":222,"end":226,"text":"Noida"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":204,"end":217,"text":"Birla Hospital"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":0,"end":6,"text":"Madhuri"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482317000,"last_updated_at":1576482317000,"sec_taken":23,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Defer decision on EP eval to primary cardiologist Dr. Gandhi,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":54,"end":59,"text":"Gandhi"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482643000,"last_updated_at":1576482643000,"sec_taken":5,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "They interviewed the patient and involved a consult to Salil Medical store.,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":55,"end":73,"text":"Salil Medical store"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482840000,"last_updated_at":1576482840000,"sec_taken":7,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mrs. Radhika Mishra is a lovely 73yo woman who presented in 3/29 with 3 days of epigastric and chest pain and was found to have a STEMI.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":5,"end":18,"text":"Radhika Mishra"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482864000,"last_updated_at":1576482864000,"sec_taken":6,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Defer decision on EP eval to primary cardiologist Dr. Gupta,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":54,"end":58,"text":"Gupta"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482883000,"last_updated_at":1576482883000,"sec_taken":5,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "If increases by more than 3 pounds , please call Dr. Angad .,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":53,"end":57,"text":"Angad"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481662000,"last_updated_at":1576481662000,"sec_taken":7,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Anita is a 75 year old living in Barely with a long history of coronary artery disease who presents with unstable angina.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":0,"end":4,"text":"Anita"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482740000,"last_updated_at":1576482740000,"sec_taken":10,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Abdominal aortic aneurysm repair , nonQ-wave myocardial infarction by enzymes at Surmati Medical Center, Srinagar.,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":105,"end":112,"text":"Srinagar"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":81,"end":102,"text":"Surmati Medical Center"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482714000,"last_updated_at":1576482714000,"sec_taken":36,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "He was transferred to Bhagalpur General Medical Center for further management.,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":32,"end":53,"text":"General Medical Center"}]},{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":22,"end":30,"text":"Bhagalpur"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481634000,"last_updated_at":1576481634000,"sec_taken":28,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "He presents originally to the Shahid Bhagat Memorial Hospital Health Services ER where he was treated with IV nitroglycerin and heparin and had recurring chest pain.,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":30,"end":76,"text":"Shahid Bhagat Memorial Hospital Health Services"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482438000,"last_updated_at":1576482438000,"sec_taken":22,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "At the National University Hospital, Warangal he ruled in for myocardial infarction with CKs in the low 300s , MB of 29.8.,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":37,"end":44,"text":"Warangal"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":7,"end":34,"text":"National University Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482662000,"last_updated_at":1576482662000,"sec_taken":17,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "He lives with his wife , former employee of the Cummins Women Commuinity Hospital, Ratnagiri,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":83,"end":91,"text":"Ratnagiri"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":48,"end":80,"text":"Cummins Women Commuinity Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482510000,"last_updated_at":1576482510000,"sec_taken":13,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Rajiv was successfully and rapidly weaned from the intra-aortic balloon pump and readmitted to the cardiology  Tananji Hwy. , Thane , New Panvel 400012 service on 25 of August,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":126,"end":130,"text":"Thane"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":0,"end":4,"text":"Rajiv"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576483119000,"last_updated_at":1576483119000,"sec_taken":21,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Sheetal is a 63-year-old female with multiple medical problems admitted 5/27/06 after ventricular VFib arrest with AICD discharge and associated fall on Coumadin.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":0,"end":6,"text":"Sheetal"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481829000,"last_updated_at":1576481829000,"sec_taken":7,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Pragati was admitted to the MICU on the Neurosurgical Service, Indore from 5/27/06 to 5/23/06 without operative intervention.,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":63,"end":68,"text":"Indore"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":28,"end":31,"text":"MICU"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":0,"end":6,"text":"Pragati"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482293000,"last_updated_at":1576482293000,"sec_taken":35,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Smita, a 63-year-old woman with traumatic contusion , subdural hemorrhage and subarachnoid hemorrhage now encephalopathic with hepatotoxicity and acute on chronic renal insufficiency with volume overload in the setting of longstanding cardiomyopathy.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":0,"end":4,"text":"Smita"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481723000,"last_updated_at":1576481723000,"sec_taken":11,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Question of  nticoagulation to be readdrissed with Dr. Sudhir in one month.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":55,"end":60,"text":"Sudhir"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482450000,"last_updated_at":1576482450000,"sec_taken":34,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Dr. Girish Dare of the cardiac consultation service followed the patient in house and felt that the reversal of her wall motion abnormalities could be attributable to the acute effects of alcoholic cardiotoxicity.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":14,"text":"Girish Dare"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482624000,"last_updated_at":1576482624000,"sec_taken":8,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mr. Shroff is a 70-year-old man with coronary artery disease status post stenting in July of this year , congestive heart failure and head and neck squamous cell carcinoma treated with chemotherapy and radiation therapy earlier this year , presenting with a change in mental status and dyspnea.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":9,"text":"Shroff"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482972000,"last_updated_at":1576482972000,"sec_taken":8,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mr. Manas is being discharged to rehab at Himalaya Hospital, Silchar and he will follow up with Dr. Tanushree Dutta, his oncologist.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":100,"end":114,"text":"Tanushree Dutta"}]},{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":61,"end":67,"text":"Silchar"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":42,"end":58,"text":"Himalaya Hospital"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":8,"text":"Manas"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481892000,"last_updated_at":1576481892000,"sec_taken":21,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The possibility of DNR/DNI was discussed at length with the patient and with his family and they repeatedly and ultimately decided to have Mr. Ravi Dubey be DNR/DNI at this point.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":143,"end":152,"text":"Ravi Dubey"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482460000,"last_updated_at":1576482460000,"sec_taken":9,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient is a 68-year-old female named Sarita with history of hypertension , diabetes mellitus , asthma , postpartum DVT/PE who presented with chest pain to Mohintara Hospital, Shimla.,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":180,"end":185,"text":"Shimla"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":160,"end":177,"text":"Mohintara Hospital"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":42,"end":47,"text":"Sarita"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482018000,"last_updated_at":1576482018000,"sec_taken":20,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Follow-up appointments with Dr. Maio 652 042-3264 in five to six weeks , Dr. Sarika her PCP in one to two weeks and Dr. Isha  in one to two weeks.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":120,"end":123,"text":"Isha"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":77,"end":82,"text":"Sarika"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":32,"end":35,"text":"Maio"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482218000,"last_updated_at":1576482218000,"sec_taken":14,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Call PCP/cardiologist at Narmada Hospital, Bhilai cardiac surgery service at 282-008-4347 with any questions.,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":43,"end":48,"text":"Bhilai"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":25,"end":40,"text":"Narmada Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482676000,"last_updated_at":1576482676000,"sec_taken":12,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient is a 58 year old right handed female named Sunita with a history of hypertension who was in her usual state of health until 10 a.m. when she noted , while in a seated position , after bending over to pick up articles from the floor , had a sudden headache described as a bifrontal burning sensation.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":55,"end":60,"text":"Sunita"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482486000,"last_updated_at":1576482486000,"sec_taken":14,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "She grew up in Satara,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":15,"end":20,"text":"Satara"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482186000,"last_updated_at":1576482186000,"sec_taken":8,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient is a 50 year old male named Saurabh who was mugged on Friday , 6/1/91.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":40,"end":46,"text":"Saurabh"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481733000,"last_updated_at":1576481733000,"sec_taken":21,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient was admitted to the Orthopedic Surgery Service under Dr. Gaurav,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":69,"end":74,"text":"Gaurav"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":32,"end":57,"text":"Orthopedic Surgery Service"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576483153000,"last_updated_at":1576483153000,"sec_taken":16,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "This is a 77-year-old female named Sudha who was transferred originally from an outside hospital for continued care after a fascial dehiscence status post subtotal colectomy.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":35,"end":39,"text":"Sudha"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481653000,"last_updated_at":1576481653000,"sec_taken":9,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient is an 83-year-old male named Ritik with past medical history significant for insulin-dependent diabetes mellitus , paroxysmal atrial fibrillation , severe aortic stenosis and moderate MR. His symptoms also consisted of dyspnea on exertion.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":41,"end":45,"text":"Ritik"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482355000,"last_updated_at":1576482355000,"sec_taken":37,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient lives at Gazipur , has remote history of smoking , quit 30 years ago.,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":21,"end":27,"text":"Gazipur"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482637000,"last_updated_at":1576482637000,"sec_taken":11,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Dr. Kartikeyan 282-008-4347 in five to six weeks ,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":13,"text":"Kartikeyan"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482203000,"last_updated_at":1576482203000,"sec_taken":6,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Dr. Asangi 374-517-1782 in one week ,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":9,"text":"Asangi"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576483002000,"last_updated_at":1576483002000,"sec_taken":8,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Dr. Parmar 709-089-4125 in 1-2 weeks.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":9,"text":"Parmar"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482225000,"last_updated_at":1576482225000,"sec_taken":6,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "To do plan make all follow-up appointments , local wound care , wash wounds daily with soap and water , watch all wounds for signs of infection ( redness , swelling , fever , pain , or discharge ) and call PCP/cardiologist at Nandan Cardiac Surgery Service at 282-008-4347 with any questions.,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":226,"end":255,"text":"Nandan Cardiac Surgery Service"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576483078000,"last_updated_at":1576483078000,"sec_taken":13,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mr. Nitesh Tiwari is a 66 year-old woman with a history of type II diabetes mellitus , congestive heart failure , peripheral vascular disease who presents to us with right leg swelling , pain and tenderness times 2-3 days.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":16,"text":"Nitesh Tiwari"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482551000,"last_updated_at":1576482551000,"sec_taken":8,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Prabhat is a 60 year old , male who initially presented for an injured knee , which occurred three days ago at work.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":0,"end":6,"text":"Prabhat"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481971000,"last_updated_at":1576481971000,"sec_taken":19,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Sharayu is a 65 year old female with pneumonia , failed outpatient treatment with zithromycin.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":0,"end":6,"text":"Sharayu"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482993000,"last_updated_at":1576482993000,"sec_taken":19,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "She was to schedule an appointment with Dr. Pati for the week following discharge.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":44,"end":47,"text":"Pati"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482978000,"last_updated_at":1576482978000,"sec_taken":5,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient is a 60-year-old male named Tanveer with coronary artery disease , status post coronary artery bypass graft in 1982,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":40,"end":46,"text":"Tanveer"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481950000,"last_updated_at":1576481950000,"sec_taken":10,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient also has appointment with the Electrophysiology Service at Nandini Medical Center , Dr. Vikas Kumar , phone number 175-256-4810.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":100,"end":110,"text":"Vikas Kumar"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":71,"end":92,"text":"Nandini Medical Center"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576483171000,"last_updated_at":1576483171000,"sec_taken":16,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Please check with Dr. Vaibhav 's office regarding time of his appointment.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":22,"end":31,"text":"Vaibhav 's"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482495000,"last_updated_at":1576482495000,"sec_taken":7,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "He also has followup appointment with Dr. Ganesh Nayar , the cardiologist at Raipur .,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":77,"end":82,"text":"Raipur"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":42,"end":53,"text":"Ganesh Nayar"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576481904000,"last_updated_at":1576481904000,"sec_taken":34,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mr. Mohan is a 75-year-old gentleman with history of insulin-dependent diabetes and hyperlipidemia who had a history of myocardial infarction and stent placement of his right coronary artery in 1/29 .,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":8,"text":"Mohan"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482615000,"last_updated_at":1576482615000,"sec_taken":20,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mr. Shakti Hari also received 2 units of packed red blood cells postoperatively for postoperative anemia.,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":9,"text":"Shakti"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482542000,"last_updated_at":1576482542000,"sec_taken":5,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mr. Mayank was screened by physical therapy for rehab and was cleared for discharge to rehabilitation on 9/10/06 .,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":9,"text":"Mayank"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576482536000,"last_updated_at":1576482536000,"sec_taken":6,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Essentially , Mr. Aadarsh is a 60 year old male who noted the onset of dark urine during early January,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":18,"end":24,"text":"Aadarsh"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505580000,"last_updated_at":1576505580000,"sec_taken":7,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "He underwent CT and ERCP at the Lisonatemi Faylandsburgnic, Community Hospital with a stent placement and resolution of jaundice,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":32,"end":77,"text":"Lisonatemi Faylandsburgnic, Community Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490462000,"last_updated_at":1576490462000,"sec_taken":115,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "He underwent an ECHO and endoscopy at Ingree and Ot of Weamanshy Medical Center on April 28,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":55,"end":78,"text":"Weamanshy Medical Center"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490148000,"last_updated_at":1576490148000,"sec_taken":8,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Basically , patient underwent a subtotal gastrectomy on the 7th of June by Dr. Abhay,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":79,"end":83,"text":"Abhay"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490471000,"last_updated_at":1576490471000,"sec_taken":8,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mrs. Aabha 75 year old female was transferred from Iming Medical Center for angioplasty,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":51,"end":70,"text":"Iming Medical Center"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":5,"end":9,"text":"Aabha"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490555000,"last_updated_at":1576490555000,"sec_taken":15,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The cardiology consult also spoke to the patient 's primary medical doctor , Dr. Kaajal in Clear La who related that the patient had had two large esophageal ulcers and a history of polycythemia vera in the past,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":81,"end":86,"text":"Kaajal"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505918000,"last_updated_at":1576505918000,"sec_taken":16,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Dr. Kaajal was on vacation , however Dr. Rohit , his partner was in the office and went through Mr. ABHINAV 's old chart and noted that Dr. Blood had performed esophagogastroduodenoscopy on the patient during his North Carolina admission for an acute upper gastrointestinal bleed,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":213,"end":226,"text":"North Carolina"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":140,"end":144,"text":"Blood"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":100,"end":109,"text":"ABHINAV 's"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":41,"end":45,"text":"Rohit"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":9,"text":"Kaajal"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576491322000,"last_updated_at":1576491322000,"sec_taken":25,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The principal operating surgeon was Dr. Aditi Sharma with the assistance of Dr. Kiriti,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":80,"end":85,"text":"Kiriti"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":40,"end":51,"text":"Aditi Sharma"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505018000,"last_updated_at":1576505018000,"sec_taken":9,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "She will be followed by her physician at Cean , Dr. Aanchal , for further pressure management and follow up of the femoral hematoma,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":52,"end":58,"text":"Aanchal"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490762000,"last_updated_at":1576490762000,"sec_taken":14,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mr. Heamnt is a 77 year old male with squamous cell carcinoma of the lung,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":9,"text":"Heamnt"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490907000,"last_updated_at":1576490907000,"sec_taken":13,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "On physical examination , Mr. Hemant had very marked inspiratory and expiratory stridor,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":30,"end":35,"text":"Hemant"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505522000,"last_updated_at":1576505522000,"sec_taken":6,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "A bronchoscopy with the intention of coring out tumor was carried out by Dr. Rajesh , but all the tumor was extrinsic to the airway and he was unable to relieve the obstruction,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":77,"end":82,"text":"Rajesh"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505097000,"last_updated_at":1576505097000,"sec_taken":6,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient was also seen by Dr. Lavangi the Oncology Service who did not feel that chemotherapy had anything of promise to offer,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":33,"end":39,"text":"Lavangi"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505153000,"last_updated_at":1576505153000,"sec_taken":5,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mr. Nilkamal is a 65 year old male who , in 1986 , had a coronary artery bypass grafting procedure at Noughwell Entanbon Health in Stoningi , Kansas,","annotation":[{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":142,"end":147,"text":"Kansas"}]},{"label":["GPE"],"points":[{"start":131,"end":138,"text":"Stoningi"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":102,"end":126,"text":"Noughwell Entanbon Health"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":11,"text":"Nilkamal"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490224000,"last_updated_at":1576490224000,"sec_taken":33,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "He underwent aortic valve replacement with a porcine valve by Dr. Gaurav,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":66,"end":71,"text":"Gaurav"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505025000,"last_updated_at":1576505025000,"sec_taken":5,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Following this , he was followed closely by Dr. Bikram in Na,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":48,"end":53,"text":"Bikram"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576491284000,"last_updated_at":1576491284000,"sec_taken":5,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "On April 8 , 1993 , Dr. Gaurav performed open heart surgery,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":24,"end":29,"text":"Gaurav"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490915000,"last_updated_at":1576490915000,"sec_taken":7,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mrs. Lakshmi is a 65 year old male who sustained a small myocardial infarction first in 1978 , with course thereafter including a coronary artery bypass graft by Dr. naina at Noughwell Entanbon Health in 1986,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":175,"end":199,"text":"Noughwell Entanbon Health"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":166,"end":170,"text":"naina"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":5,"end":11,"text":"Lakshmi"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490336000,"last_updated_at":1576490336000,"sec_taken":17,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Dr. Tahir did not feel the patient had an increased risk for repeat urinary tract infection,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":8,"text":"Tahir"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576504949000,"last_updated_at":1576504949000,"sec_taken":5,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Aerobic Inhaler 2 puffs bid ; Proventil Inhaler 2 puffs 6-7 times per day on prn basis ; Motrin 800 mg PO tid , patient discontinued this prior to his admission ; Hydrin , patient takes this for voiding , which was prescribed by Dr. Tapendra,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":233,"end":240,"text":"Tapendra"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490623000,"last_updated_at":1576490623000,"sec_taken":25,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mr. Maadhavi is a 59 year old female , admitted to the Fairm of Ijordcompmac Hospital with chest pain during stage 1 of an exercise tolerance test,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":11,"text":"Maadhavi"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505364000,"last_updated_at":1576505364000,"sec_taken":6,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient was taken to the Nilame Hospital Cardiac Surgical Intensive Care Unit in stable condition , where she had an uneventful immediate postoperative course,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":29,"end":43,"text":"Nilame Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576504904000,"last_updated_at":1576504904000,"sec_taken":21,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "She will be followed by her cardiologist , Dr. Lavanya , her local medical doctor at the ASDH , Dr. Mahadev Vera , and Dr. Gajendra of the Endocrinology Service,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":123,"end":130,"text":"Gajendra"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":100,"end":111,"text":"Mahadev Vera"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":47,"end":53,"text":"Lavanya"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490683000,"last_updated_at":1576490683000,"sec_taken":15,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mr. Harsh is a 52 year old female who underwent removal of a right psoas muscle for retroperitoneal sarcoma in 03/92,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":8,"text":"Harsh"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505992000,"last_updated_at":1576505992000,"sec_taken":4,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient will follow up with Dr. Mithlesh,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":36,"end":43,"text":"Mithlesh"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576504850000,"last_updated_at":1576504850000,"sec_taken":10,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient is to have Santea Gehawhi General Hospital,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":23,"end":53,"text":"Santea Gehawhi General Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505900000,"last_updated_at":1576505900000,"sec_taken":6,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mrs. Vaanika is a fifty year old black gentleman with a long history of hepatitis C , believed to be contracted during transfusions in a previous trauma,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":5,"end":11,"text":"Vaanika"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576491295000,"last_updated_at":1576491295000,"sec_taken":10,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "This 68 year old female had rheumatic fever in the past , and has had chronic atrial fibrillation,","annotation":null,"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576754469000,"last_updated_at":1576754469000,"sec_taken":0,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mrs. Niharika is a 44 year-old right handed woman with Down 's syndrome who presents with falling and a decrease in her activities of daily living,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":5,"end":12,"text":"Niharika"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505411000,"last_updated_at":1576505411000,"sec_taken":6,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient was admitted to the Arkzie- Memorial for lumbar puncture,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":32,"end":47,"text":"Arkzie- Memorial"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505139000,"last_updated_at":1576505139000,"sec_taken":7,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient was discharged to home on 11/15/02 with instructions to the family to observe her gait in her home environment and to observe her behavior in her home environment over the next day and to report back to the primary neurologist , Dr. Firoz , as to changes,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":245,"end":249,"text":"Firoz"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490270000,"last_updated_at":1576490270000,"sec_taken":20,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mrs. Nirupama, 68 year old female has rheumatic heart disease,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":5,"end":12,"text":"Nirupama"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576506487000,"last_updated_at":1576506487000,"sec_taken":5,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mitral and possibly tricuspid valve surgery is scheduled for Labor Day by Dr. Raj Kumar,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":78,"end":86,"text":"Raj Kumar"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576506221000,"last_updated_at":1576506221000,"sec_taken":4,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The interventional neuro-radiology procedure was performed by Dr. Ananya , on August 22 , via the right femoral artery,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":66,"end":71,"text":"Ananya"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505009000,"last_updated_at":1576505009000,"sec_taken":10,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mr. Balmukund 68-year-old patient of Dr. Nilesh Jaiswal had two episodes of rheumatic fever as a teenager,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":41,"end":54,"text":"Nilesh Jaiswal"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":12,"text":"Balmukund"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576491177000,"last_updated_at":1576491177000,"sec_taken":11,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mrs. Aditi 61 year old woman was transferred from the Iming Medical Center because of alleged intractible ascites,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":54,"end":73,"text":"Iming Medical Center"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":5,"end":9,"text":"Aditi"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505652000,"last_updated_at":1576505652000,"sec_taken":10,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient was seen in preoperative consultation by Dr. Madhu Kumari , on November 4 , 1992,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":57,"end":68,"text":"Madhu Kumari"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505101000,"last_updated_at":1576505101000,"sec_taken":4,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "During her recent hospitalization at Iming Medical Center , she was noted to have marked abdominal distension , felt to be due to ascites,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":37,"end":56,"text":"Iming Medical Center"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505456000,"last_updated_at":1576505456000,"sec_taken":7,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mr. Kamal Kumar was a 34 year old gentleman with no significant past medical history except for a history of of intravenous drug abuse,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":8,"text":"Kamal"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490816000,"last_updated_at":1576490816000,"sec_taken":7,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "He was status post a rehabilitation hospitalization at the Raya Ma Den Erinmarg Hospital with a recent recrudescence of his drug abuse,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":59,"end":87,"text":"Raya Ma Den Erinmarg Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576506098000,"last_updated_at":1576506098000,"sec_taken":12,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "He was admitted to the Sephsandpot Center on the morning of 4/9 and was subsequently transferred to the Fairm of Ijordcompmac Hospital for further care,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":23,"end":40,"text":"Sephsandpot Center"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576506301000,"last_updated_at":1576506301000,"sec_taken":14,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "He was then transferred via Med Flight to the Fairm of Ijordcompmac Hospital,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":55,"end":75,"text":"Ijordcompmac Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505280000,"last_updated_at":1576505280000,"sec_taken":11,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The serum toxicology was positive for Cocaine on admission to the Fairm of Ijordcompmac Hospital as well as the Sephsandpot Center,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":112,"end":129,"text":"Sephsandpot Center"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":75,"end":95,"text":"Ijordcompmac Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490943000,"last_updated_at":1576490943000,"sec_taken":26,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "He was accepted at the Vo Yd Burgsygu Hospital Center Intensive Care Unit and his hospital course will be reviewed by problems,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":29,"end":45,"text":"Burgsygu Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505047000,"last_updated_at":1576505047000,"sec_taken":16,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Peritoneal dialysis was instituted on 4/11 after a Tenckhoff catheter was placed by Drs. Freierm , Le , and Round,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":89,"end":95,"text":"Freierm"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505546000,"last_updated_at":1576505546000,"sec_taken":6,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mrs. Damini is a 75 year old righthanded Caucasian female who was admitted to the Fairm of Ijordcompmac Hospital because of left facial droop and hand weakness after glaucoma laser surgery,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":5,"end":10,"text":"Damini"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505609000,"last_updated_at":1576505609000,"sec_taken":6,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "She was transferred to the Sas General Hospital for further evaluation of some weakness in the setting of multiple medical problems,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":27,"end":46,"text":"Sas General Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576504861000,"last_updated_at":1576504861000,"sec_taken":10,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "2. History of M. kansasaii with workup by Dr. Saejal at Sas General Hospital proceeding currently,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":56,"end":75,"text":"Sas General Hospital"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":46,"end":51,"text":"Saejal"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":17,"end":25,"text":"kansasaii"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576491143000,"last_updated_at":1576491143000,"sec_taken":19,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Previous echoes have shown MVP at the Ona Hospital,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":38,"end":49,"text":"Ona Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490248000,"last_updated_at":1576490248000,"sec_taken":5,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mr. Harish is a 57 year old male , who was admitted for right total hip replacement,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":9,"text":"Harish"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576506167000,"last_updated_at":1576506167000,"sec_taken":8,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "In 1990 , Mr. Harish was involved in an motor vehicle accident in which he sustained a fractured dislocation of his right hip , a fracture of his right shoulder and some fractured ribs,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":14,"end":19,"text":"Harish"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505539000,"last_updated_at":1576505539000,"sec_taken":8,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "On that same day , 11/11/90 , he underwent open reduction , internal fixation of a right acetabular fracture performed by Dr. Ashok Kumar,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":126,"end":136,"text":"Ashok Kumar"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505300000,"last_updated_at":1576505300000,"sec_taken":6,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Dr. Sahiba felt the patient was stable from a pulmonary standpoint , and recommended a short course of steroids immediately preoperatively in the perioperative period,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":9,"text":"Sahiba"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576491229000,"last_updated_at":1576491229000,"sec_taken":9,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient was seen by Dr. Nie Threatsjescdreps at the Fairm of Ijordcompmac Hospital in consult,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":65,"end":85,"text":"Ijordcompmac Hospital"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":28,"end":30,"text":"Nie"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490654000,"last_updated_at":1576490654000,"sec_taken":13,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Review by Dr. Lokesh , who felt no further cardiac evaluation was required,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":14,"end":19,"text":"Lokesh"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576506016000,"last_updated_at":1576506016000,"sec_taken":3,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Patient had pulmonary function tests under the car of Dr. Mahndra Srikant,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":58,"end":72,"text":"Mahndra Srikant"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505448000,"last_updated_at":1576505448000,"sec_taken":5,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mr. Harish was seen by Dr. Mahendra Srikant , from Pulmonary in regards to his pulmonary function,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":27,"end":42,"text":"Mahendra Srikant"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":9,"text":"Harish"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505987000,"last_updated_at":1576505987000,"sec_taken":17,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Dr. Sahiba felt the patient was able to undergo an anesthetic , and total hip replacement , and recommended Solu-Medrol 20 mg to be given intravenously immediately preoperatively , and q6h for 4 doses postoperatively,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":9,"text":"Sahiba"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490869000,"last_updated_at":1576490869000,"sec_taken":10,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Dr. Tanvir felt that the patient was not at increase for urinary tract infection , and recommended proceeding with surgery,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":9,"text":"Tanvir"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505241000,"last_updated_at":1576505241000,"sec_taken":6,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient was admitted to the Fairm of Ijordcompmac Hospital for further evaluation and definite treatment of his cardiac disease , as well as evaluation of his chronic renal insufficiency and multiple medical problems,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":41,"end":61,"text":"Ijordcompmac Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505252000,"last_updated_at":1576505252000,"sec_taken":7,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mr. Ear did well in the postoperative period and continued to be followed closely by the Cardiology , Renal , and Diabetes and Cardiac Surgery Services,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":6,"text":"Ear"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490110000,"last_updated_at":1576490110000,"sec_taken":10,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient was then extubated on the second postoperative day in the Surgical Intensive Care Unit,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":70,"end":97,"text":"Surgical Intensive Care Unit"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576506591000,"last_updated_at":1576506591000,"sec_taken":8,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Dr. Freiermthalskush felt that this represented an appropriate improvement in the patient 's acute tubular necrosis , and that he was probably approaching his baseline renal function,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":19,"text":"Freiermthalskush"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576504959000,"last_updated_at":1576504959000,"sec_taken":14,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Dr. Kotekeese , the patient's diabetes consultant , noted that the patient 's morning regular insulin was new , and suggested that a premixed NPH regular 70/30 insulin might prove to be appropriate for him,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":12,"text":"Kotekeese"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505678000,"last_updated_at":1576505678000,"sec_taken":6,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient is to follow up with Dr. Bun and with Dr. Shufffyfe,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":54,"end":62,"text":"Shufffyfe"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":37,"end":39,"text":"Bun"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576491198000,"last_updated_at":1576491198000,"sec_taken":12,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mr. Himanshu is a 76 year old white male with a probable brachial artery embolism,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":11,"text":"Himanshu"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505956000,"last_updated_at":1576505956000,"sec_taken":5,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The surgeon was Dr. Hitesh and first assistant Dr. Home,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":51,"end":54,"text":"Home"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":20,"end":25,"text":"Hitesh"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505572000,"last_updated_at":1576505572000,"sec_taken":13,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "He recommended that the patient be heparinized as the Scabeth T Hospital Surgery Team had already done and that Coumadinization be begun within a few days of heparinization,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":54,"end":71,"text":"Scabeth T Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505509000,"last_updated_at":1576505509000,"sec_taken":11,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "It has been a pleasure serving Mr. Himanshu and taking care of him,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":35,"end":42,"text":"Himanshu"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505291000,"last_updated_at":1576505291000,"sec_taken":3,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "He is a very pleasant gentleman and it has also been a pleasure to deal with his primary medical doctor , Dr. Hema who is very accessible,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":110,"end":113,"text":"Hema"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505029000,"last_updated_at":1576505029000,"sec_taken":4,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mrs. Saanvi Seth is a 73 year old Gravida 6 Para 4 abortions 2 with a background history of stage IIIC papillary serous adenocarcinoma of the ovary who presents on 5/30/94 for failure to thrive , right lower lobe pneumonia and obstructive uropathy,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":5,"end":15,"text":"Saanvi Seth"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505944000,"last_updated_at":1576505944000,"sec_taken":7,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "One month later the patient was readmitted to Fairm of Ijordcompmac Hospital for definitive debulking including total abdominal hysterectomy , bilateral salpingo-oophorectomy , omentectomy , splenectomy and ileostomy take-down by Dr. Salini Choudhary,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":234,"end":249,"text":"Salini Choudhary"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":55,"end":75,"text":"Ijordcompmac Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490640000,"last_updated_at":1576490640000,"sec_taken":16,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "She was then seen on 5/30/94 at Fairm of Ijordcompmac Hospital for a routine chemotherapy but complained of decreased urinary output , nausea and vomiting and poor appetite and was therefore admitted,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":41,"end":61,"text":"Ijordcompmac Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576504912000,"last_updated_at":1576504912000,"sec_taken":8,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient was therefore admitted to the GYN / Oncology Service under the care of Dr. Vaibhav,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":87,"end":93,"text":"Vaibhav"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":42,"end":63,"text":"GYN / Oncology Service"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490139000,"last_updated_at":1576490139000,"sec_taken":18,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "In view of these results with the elevated white blood count , elevated creatinine , Dr. Jagan felt that the patient was inadequately stented,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":89,"end":93,"text":"Jagan"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576506376000,"last_updated_at":1576506376000,"sec_taken":7,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient will follow up with Dr. Vaibhav on an out-patient basis,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":36,"end":42,"text":"Vaibhav"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505287000,"last_updated_at":1576505287000,"sec_taken":6,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mrs. Rina is a 73 year-old white female status post ileostomy and omentectomy for bowel obstruction secondary to ovarian cancer , who underwent neo adjuvant chemotherapy with Cytoxan and Cisplatin followed by total abdominal hysterectomy , bilateral salpingo-oophorectomy with formal debulking and ileostomy take down on 7/5/94 , which included splenectomy and lower anterior resection,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":5,"end":8,"text":"Rina"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505116000,"last_updated_at":1576505116000,"sec_taken":13,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Dr. Priyanka Reddy from the Urology Service was consulted in view of the above findings,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":17,"text":"Priyanka Reddy"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505357000,"last_updated_at":1576505357000,"sec_taken":10,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "During this time in January of 1992 Dr. Bahuddin had noted two distal esophageal ulcers,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":40,"end":47,"text":"Bahuddin"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576491777000,"last_updated_at":1576491777000,"sec_taken":10,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Is that of a 71 year old with 3C papillary serous adenocarcinoma , who initially had presented to the Istooksu Medical Center , at which time she had a omentectomy , and ileostomy performed,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":102,"end":124,"text":"Istooksu Medical Center"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576491331000,"last_updated_at":1576491331000,"sec_taken":8,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "His plans for follow up include a return to the Maza Alllarow Healthcare Surgery Clinic on 6-21-92 , that is two and a half weeks from the day of discharge ( 6-4-92 ),","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":48,"end":86,"text":"Maza Alllarow Healthcare Surgery Clinic"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505472000,"last_updated_at":1576505472000,"sec_taken":8,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "He is to see his primary medical doctor , Dr. Twinkle Kumari , Sapo on Tuesday , June 7 , 1992 , that is this coming Tuesday,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":46,"end":59,"text":"Twinkle Kumari"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490346000,"last_updated_at":1576490346000,"sec_taken":27,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mrs. Lalima is a 71 year old white female who was initially found to have a stenotic area in her mid-sigmoid colon on barium enema,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":5,"end":10,"text":"Lalima"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490689000,"last_updated_at":1576490689000,"sec_taken":5,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient was explored by the General Surgery Service and found to have Stage IIIC ovarian carcinoma,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":32,"end":54,"text":"General Surgery Service"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490202000,"last_updated_at":1576490202000,"sec_taken":11,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "She is instructed to follow up with Dr. Chandan's office,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":40,"end":48,"text":"Chandan's"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505257000,"last_updated_at":1576505257000,"sec_taken":13,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mrs. Nisha is a 71 year old white female with widely metastatic ovarian carcinoma , who is status post one cycle of chemotherapy with Cytoxan and cisplatin , who presents at this time for tumor debulking,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":5,"end":9,"text":"Nisha"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576491208000,"last_updated_at":1576491208000,"sec_taken":9,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient was admitted to the General Surgical Service in July of 1992,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":32,"end":55,"text":"General Surgical Service"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576506359000,"last_updated_at":1576506359000,"sec_taken":8,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient did well postoperatively and was transferred to the Gynecology / Oncology Service for chemotherapy on August 3 , 1992 ..","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":64,"end":92,"text":"Gynecology / Oncology Service"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490318000,"last_updated_at":1576490318000,"sec_taken":18,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mrs. Nisha required multiple transfusions for a decreased hematocrit postoperatively,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":5,"end":9,"text":"Nisha"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576506084000,"last_updated_at":1576506084000,"sec_taken":5,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "She will have Santea Gehawhi General Hospital assistance from the Gableslandbaltma,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":66,"end":81,"text":"Gableslandbaltma"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":14,"end":44,"text":"Santea Gehawhi General Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576506078000,"last_updated_at":1576506078000,"sec_taken":48,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The Santea Gehawhi General Hospital will draw prothrombin times to be called into the Fairm of Ijordcompmac Hospital Anticoagulation Clinic,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":117,"end":138,"text":"Anticoagulation Clinic"}]},{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":95,"end":115,"text":"Ijordcompmac Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490809000,"last_updated_at":1576490809000,"sec_taken":16,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient is instructed to telephone Dr. Chandan's office to arrange follow up visits,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":43,"end":51,"text":"Chandan's"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576491786000,"last_updated_at":1576491786000,"sec_taken":0,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mrs. Neela is a 71 year old white female with metastatic ovarian carcinoma , who recently underwent an exploratory laparotomy on 5/2 by Dr. Korcblinknud,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":140,"end":151,"text":"Korcblinknud"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":5,"end":9,"text":"Neela"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490835000,"last_updated_at":1576490835000,"sec_taken":17,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient had an ileostomy performed and had had her first course of chemotherapy and later debulking operation by Dr. Mahesh,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":121,"end":126,"text":"Mahesh"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505778000,"last_updated_at":1576505778000,"sec_taken":13,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "She complained of increased numbness of the right foot over time , and was seen at Sephsandpot Center , where she was found to have palpable right femoral and popliteal pulses , and no pedal pulses,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":83,"end":100,"text":"Sephsandpot Center"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505165000,"last_updated_at":1576505165000,"sec_taken":16,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient was transferred to the Fairm of Ijordcompmac Hospital,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":35,"end":64,"text":"Fairm of Ijordcompmac Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576754174000,"last_updated_at":1576754174000,"sec_taken":7,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mrs. Neha is a 71 year old female with stenotic section of mid sigmoid colon , shown on barium enema , also has diverticular disease,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":5,"end":8,"text":"Neha"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490298000,"last_updated_at":1576490298000,"sec_taken":8,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "She will follow up with Dr. Rajeev, her surgeon,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":28,"end":33,"text":"Rajeev"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505484000,"last_updated_at":1576505484000,"sec_taken":3,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "She will also follow up with Dr. Akash , her GYN Oncologist,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":33,"end":37,"text":"Akash"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490791000,"last_updated_at":1576490791000,"sec_taken":10,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Ms. Amit Kumar is an 86 year old female , previously healthy , who presents with a 3 month history of dysphagia,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":13,"text":"Amit Kumar"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490582000,"last_updated_at":1576490582000,"sec_taken":9,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "She was subsequently referred to Dr. Kamlesh for a possible resection of this carcinoma,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":37,"end":43,"text":"Kamlesh"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505087000,"last_updated_at":1576505087000,"sec_taken":4,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient was admitted to the Service of Dr. Faiz,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":47,"end":50,"text":"Faiz"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576504965000,"last_updated_at":1576504965000,"sec_taken":5,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "She will be discharged to home and will be seen in follow-up by her regular physicians as well as Dr. Kishan,","annotation":null,"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576491795000,"last_updated_at":1576491795000,"sec_taken":0,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mrs. Nivedita is a 68 year old female with squamous cell carcinoma of the tongue , T3 , N1 , M0 transferred from Cla Lip Operinlafo Hospital with a tracheoesophageal perforation , secondary to tracheostomy placement,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":113,"end":139,"text":"Cla Lip Operinlafo Hospital"}]},{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":5,"end":12,"text":"Nivedita"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505799000,"last_updated_at":1576505799000,"sec_taken":11,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient was given antibiotics and transferred to the Fairm of Ijordcompmac Hospital for tracheal reconstruction and evaluation of possible esophageal injury,","annotation":null,"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576506863000,"last_updated_at":1576506863000,"sec_taken":0,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The injury occurred several hours prior to admission,","annotation":null,"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576506870000,"last_updated_at":1576506870000,"sec_taken":0,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "On arrival to the Fairm of Ijordcompmac Hospital she received Kefzol and Flagyl,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":18,"end":47,"text":"Fairm of Ijordcompmac Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576754218000,"last_updated_at":1576754218000,"sec_taken":8,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "To the Valtawnprinceel Community Memorial Hospital for treatment of her tongue cancer,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":7,"end":49,"text":"Valtawnprinceel Community Memorial Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490099000,"last_updated_at":1576490099000,"sec_taken":10,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mrs. Puja is a 72 year old female with known carotid stenosis , and recent carotid noninvasives at an outside hospital , which showed 90% left sided stenosis,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":5,"end":8,"text":"Puja"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576506028000,"last_updated_at":1576506028000,"sec_taken":7,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "The patient was admitted to the Tau Memorial Hospital,","annotation":[{"label":["ORG"],"points":[{"start":32,"end":52,"text":"Tau Memorial Hospital"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576504931000,"last_updated_at":1576504931000,"sec_taken":5,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "She was seen by Dr. Rahul Sachan of the renal service for management of her chronic renal insufficiency,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":20,"end":31,"text":"Rahul Sachan"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505497000,"last_updated_at":1576505497000,"sec_taken":16,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mrs. Madhuri is a 66 year old white female with metastatic colon carcinoma with a mass in the left superhilar region , who presents for bronchoscopy , mediastinal exploration and resection,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":5,"end":11,"text":"Madhuri"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576490778000,"last_updated_at":1576490778000,"sec_taken":14,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Follow up with Dr. Prince,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":19,"end":24,"text":"Prince"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505670000,"last_updated_at":1576505670000,"sec_taken":16,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mrs. Madhumati is a 65 year old female , status post a right colectomy for colon cancer , now with some question of hepatic metastases,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":5,"end":13,"text":"Madhumati"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576491352000,"last_updated_at":1576491352000,"sec_taken":14,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Dr. Babita Kumari of the Radiology Service performed intraoperative ultrasound , and carefully looked at the entire liver,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":16,"text":"Babita Kumari"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505515000,"last_updated_at":1576505515000,"sec_taken":5,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
{"content": "Mr. Anish is 75 year old Hispanic male with insulin dependent diabetes mellitus and peripheral vascular disease , status post a middle cerebral artery cerebrovascular accident was admitted for left carotid endarterectomy,","annotation":[{"label":["PERSON"],"points":[{"start":4,"end":8,"text":"Anish"}]}],"extras":null,"metadata":{"first_done_at":1576505398000,"last_updated_at":1576505398000,"sec_taken":4,"last_updated_by":"USifJcqQhoYUGypCchuVNNhTmoI2","status":"done","evaluation":"NONE"}}
